techfetch.com 2012-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Corp-Corp

| 

Corp-Corp.com (“we” or “us”) is committed to protecting any personal information that you provide to us through web sites owned and operated by Corp-Corp.com, including [http://www.corp-corp.com](http://www.corp-corp.com/) (the “Web Site”). We believe it is important for you to know how we protect your personal information to deliver you the best user experience possible. This Privacy Policy pertains to information that is collected online, unless otherwise noted herein.

BY USING THE WEB SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE WEB SITE.

  1. ## Information We Collect

We collect two types of information about you when you visit our Web Site: personally identifiable information and non-personal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our Site that you have visited and your IP address).

**_(A) Personally Identifiable Information_**

“Personally Identifiable Information” is information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address, citizenship / visa status, telephone number, fax number, email address, or company name. We collect and store the personal information that you have provided to us. Here are some examples of the ways in which we may collect your personal information on the Web Site:

    * As part of your registration as a job seeker on the Web Site;
    * As part of your registration as a recruiter on the Web Site;
    * As part of entering and participating in contests and promotions;
    * When you use services or tools on the Web Site including “Forward this to a Friend” or referral features;
    * When submitting information for editorial purposes including news items, press releases, or other items of interest;
    * When you submit comments on the Web Site’s feedback page;
    * When you contact us for assistance through our 24/7 Support Center;
    * When your name, email address, telephone number, fax number are referred by another recruiter, employer, job seeker; and
    * When you are registering for events or conferences.

The above list provides an example of the personal information that may be collected by Corp-Corp.com. From time to time, we may collect personal information from you in other ways that are not described above. If you do not want us to collect your personal information, please do not provide it to us. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the personally identifiable information that you submit to Corp-Corp.com. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using our Web Site and tools and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy.

_(B) Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

Here are some examples of the non-personally identifiable information that is collected via the Web Site and a description of how this information is used:

    * **Internet Protocol (IP) address:** Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data. We use this information to deliver our Web Site to you upon request, to tailor our Web Site to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our Web Site.
    * **Cookie:** A “cookie” is a small text file placed on your computer’s hard disk that may be used to collect information about your activity on the Web Site. For example, when someone visits a page within the Web Site, a cookie is placed on the user’s machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the user has visited the Web Site previously. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our Web Site.
    * **Web Beacons** (also known as “clear gifs,” “web bugs” or “pixel tags”): “Web Beacons” are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Web Site and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted email messages, web beacons can tell the sender whether and when the email has been opened. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages.

We also may collect non-personally identifiable information from you in order to customize your experience, fulfill your requests for information, and improve our services. We may provide this non-personally identifiable information to third parties. For example, we might inform third parties about the number of users of our Web Site and the activities they conduct while on the Web Site. We also may provide trusted partners with general information regarding our users and visitors.

Finally, Corp-Corp.com may combine any public information you provide in any of the public areas on the Web Site with non-personally identifiable information to create aggregate data. This information may also be disclosed to third parties. Aggregate data does not contain any information that could be used to contact you or identify you personally.

  2. ## Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information

_(A) Personally Identifiable Information_

We may use or disclose your personal information in the following instances:

    * To allow job seekers to post resumes;
    * To allow recruiters to post job openings and search resumes. These jobs will be listed and indexed in our Web Site as well as search engines, which may be searchable either directly or indirectly by job seekers, other registered users, and corporations;
    * To allow other recruiters to contact you online via the Web Site;
    * To enable you to contact us and provide feedback, and to enable us to respond to your comments and requests for assistance;
    * To improve our marketing and advertising efforts;
    * To provide you with our own and third-party product and content offerings that may interest you including newsletters, surveys and career advice;
    * To enable you to use the “Forward this to a Friend” and “Referral” features;
    * To enable unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents, or independent contractors to help us maintain our Web Site and to provide any other administrative service to us (including, but not limited to, hosting our web servers, providing market research analysis, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance);
    * To affiliates, strategic partners, agents, third party marketers or other unaffiliated parties who are offering products or services that we believe may be of interest to you or who require your personally identifiable information for research, administrative and/or internal business purposes. These parties may use your personally identifiable information to contact you with an offer or advertisement related to a product or service, or they may use such information for their own research, administration or business purposes. If you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information in this manner, please do not provide us with this information;
    * To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets;
    * To send account statements and invoices to users;
    * To comply with the law or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform or comply with the law or with legal process served on us;
    * To enforce or apply any of the terms of our user agreements;
    * To protect and defend our rights and property, and to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our users;
    * To contact you about Web Site updates, informational and service-related communications, including important security updates;
    * To generate internal reports about the use of our Web Site;
    * To publish the jobs in third party job feed sites;
    * To post jobs and upload resumes received through E-Mails, XML Feeds, and APIs.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise use, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties.

All recruiters who pay for access to the Web Site may access your resume. We use our best efforts to grant access to these database services only to recruiters, headhunters, staffing firms, and employment search consultants. However, we cannot guarantee that other parties will not, without our consent, gain access to these services.

You may remove your resume or corporate profile from our Web Site at any time. However, parties with authorized access to the Web Site may have retained a copy of your resume or corporate profile in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes or corporate profiles in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes and corporate profiles by any of such parties while resumes and corporate profiles are in their database.

Even your resume or corporate profile from our web site is removed, there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, logs, and other records. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes. However, Corp-Corp.com reserves the right, to re-contact former users of our web site.

_(B) Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

Non-personally identifiable information is used and disclosed as described above and in other ways as permitted by applicable laws, including combining non-personally identifiable information with personally identifiable information.

  3. ## Suggestions You Make to Us

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any content, business information, ideas, concepts or inventions that you may elect to send to Corp-Corp.com by email or post anywhere on the Web Site. If you want to keep content or business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them in an email to Corp-Corp.com or post them in any way.

  4. ## Children Under the Age of 13

Neither Corp-Corp.com nor its Web Site are designed or intended for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.

  5. ## Links to Third Party Sites

From time to time, Corp-Corp.com may offer you content through a web site hosted and operated by a third party. In addition, the Web Site may contain links to other third party web sites operated by companies that are not affiliated with Corp-Corp.com and that do not have contracts to provide content or services through Corp-Corp.com. These links may be found in advertisements, referenced within content, or placed beside the names or logos of sponsors. If you choose to link to one of these third party web sites, you should review the privacy policy posted on such a web site to understand how that web site collects and uses your personally identifiable information.

Corp-Corp.com hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties.

  6. ## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the “last update” date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change by sending a notice to the primary email address specified by you, placing a notification on the Web Site login screen, or by placing a prominent notice on the Web Site.

  7. ## How Corp-Corp.com Handles Privacy and Security Internally

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you understand that any information that you transfer to us is done at your own risk.

We take all reasonable measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information remains as secure as reasonably possible. Corp-Corp.com maintains industry standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information that you provide to us.

  8. ## Opt In / Opt Out Policy

We respect your privacy and your ability to choose whether to share or not share information with Corp-Corp.com or any third party. When jobs seekers or companies opt to register at Corp-Corp.com, a business relationship is created between Corp-Corp.com and that job seeker or company. Examples of how a business relationship may be created through registration include, but are not necessarily limited to: submitting a resume, applying for a Trial Membership Subscription, or purchasing a Subscription.

You may choose to “opt-out” of sharing Personal Information in several ways. When choosing to use certain features or services on the Site, you can choose whether or not to share optional Personal Information in connection with the feature or service. If you receive communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt out from receiving these communications, either by specifically indicating this preference in a communication to us via email or letter or by deleting your registration profile from our database and terminating your business relationship with Corp-Corp.com.

  9. ## Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding Corp-Corp.com’s disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us:

Corp-Corp.com  
13755, Sunrise Valley Drive,   
#725, Herndon, VA 20171

  10. ## International Transfer of Information

If you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, Corp-Corp.com may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to:

    * the use of your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
    * the transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States as indicated above.

  11. ## Contacting Corp-Corp.com

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please email   
Support at Corp-Corp.com. All information you provide in any written communication will also be covered by this policy.

Last Updated: Aug-2010
